(Leonard:)- Thank you.
- Honey, why did you get a loom?
(Sheldon:)I was working with luminous fish
and I thought, "Hey...
...loom."
(Sheldon:)Mom, what are you doing here?
(Mrs Cooper:)Leonard called me.
(Sheldon:)I know, but why?
(Leonard:)Because one of the great minds
of the 21 st century...
(Leonard:)...is raising glow-in-the-dark fish
and weaving serapes.
This is not a serape. This is a poncho.
A serape is open at the sides,
a poncho is closed. This is a poncho.
(Sheldon:)And neither is a reason
to call someone's mother.
(Leonard:)Really?
When was the last time you left the house?
(Sheldon:)I went to the market with Penny.
Yeah, that was three weeks ago.
(Sheldon:)Well, then, buckle up.
(Sheldon:)In the next four to eight days,
she's going to get very crabby.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sweetheart,
your little friend is concerned about you.
(Sheldon:)Yes, well, I'm not a child.
(Sheldon:)I'm a grown man
capable of living my life as I see fit.